Brendan Vize

Contact information: Email: brendan@bvize.com

Profile:

Experienced call centre supervisor with a demonstrated history of customer service. Skilled in leadership and coaching. A Strong analytical thinker, problem-solver, and communicator with a Masters degree in Philosophy and a Professional Diploma of Digital Marketing.

Previous Experience:

Jan 2018- Present Globetech/Apple

Cork

Data Analyst

Sept 2017- Dec 2017 Abtran/Irish Life Health

Cork

Support Agent

Jan 2013- Jul 2017 Wallis Market and Social Research

Melbourne

Contact Centre Supervisor

- Lead team of 30 agents
- Monitored call centre metrics in a high pressure multi-project environment
- Advice and support for business and academic stakeholders

July 2012- Jun 2017 Monash University

Melbourne

Researcher/Tutor

- Analysis and communication of complex information
- Mentoring and support for students
- Working independently with minimal supervision

Feb 2014- May 2016 Deakin University

Melbourne

University Tutor

Feb 2013- Mar 2016 The School of Life

Melbourne

Content Writer/ Workshop Facilitator

- Wrote and presented content for public events
- Completed multiple small projects to strict deadlines

Nov 2010 – Feb 2012 Inland Revenue Department Wellington

Customer Service Representative (Contact Centre)

Feb 2009 – Nov 2011 Victoria University (VUW)

Wellington

University Tutor

Feb 2008 – Jan 2009 UCMS Ltd.

Melbourne

Customer Service Representative (Contact Centre)

Feb 2007 – Nov 2007 Capital Communications Group Ltd

Edinburgh

Contact Centre Supervisor

Education/Qualifications:

2018 Digital Marketing Institute

Cork

Professional Diploma of Digital Marketing

2009- 2011 Victoria University (VUW)

Wellington

Master of Arts (MA) in Philosophy

2005 Victoria University (VUW)

Wellington

Honours (BA Hons) in Philosophy

1999-2001 Victoria University (VUW)

Wellington

Bachelor of Arts (BA) in Philosophy and Religious Studies